goguides.org 2015-06-16

# GoGuides - Privacy Policy

GoGuides, Inc. respects and protects your privacy, when you are using our free GoGuides Search and Directory. Information that may specifically identify you as an individual is never collected nor shared with third parties.

GoGuides and Cookies

Upon your first visit to GoGuides, GoGuides may send a "cookie" to your computer. Cookies are used by many sites and an internet search on 'cookies' may provide you with more information. The intent of cookies is to identify your computer preferences and searching patterns. GoGuides will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most internet browser are set up to accept cookies. Although it is possible to reset your computer settings to inform you of cookie or to reject cookies, such actions may interfere with your searches at GoGuides.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to GoGuides.  
Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on visits to GoGuides and/or other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).  
You can also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

What Information Do We Collect?

GoGuides does not secretly collect information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information during the site submission process. This information is used to contact you if there is a need for a revision to your site reviews. GoGuides notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. This information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.

Links to Other Sites

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by GoGuides searches are developed by people over whom GoGuides has no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. It is important that you preview their Privacy Policy and remove any cookies from your computer if you have any concerns.

GoGuides Shared Information

GoGuides may share information about you with advertisers, sponsors, and other third parties. This shared information is in the form of compiled data that does not identify individuals. For example, we may disclose keyword searches, or the amount of time spent in searching at GoGuides. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy

By using the GoGuides Search and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this policy and to our [Terms of Service Policy](http://www.goguides.org/info/legal.html). GoGuides may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such changes will be dated and posted on this page. The purpose of this Policy is to make you an informed Internet user - fully aware of what information is collected and the uses for complied information.

Additional questions?

If you still have questions feel free to contact us. Our email address is Team Support - [teamsupport@goguides.org](mailto:teamsupport@goguides.org)
